binverse.com 2010-03-06

# Binverse Privacy Policy

##  PRIVACY POLICY

At Binverse (the "Company," “Binverse,” "us," "we," or "our"), we recognize that many visitors to our site are concerned about how we treat any information that they may provide to us. Since we respect the privacy of our customers, we have established this Privacy Policy. We are providing you with this policy statement to inform you of the kinds of information we may gather during your visit to the Binverse site (the "Site"), why we gather customer information, what we use the information for, under what circumstances we may disclose such information, and how you can instruct us to limit the use of that information. We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time, so you should review it periodically. 

_Note: You must be 18 years old or older to register as a customer of Binverse._

If you have any questions please contact our Customer Service Team. You may also write to us at: 

2125 Center Avenue Suite 507  
Fort Lee, NJ 07024  
USA

This privacy policy only applies to Binverse services. 

##  WHAT INFORMATION WE GATHER 

To use Binverse’s services, you must register as a user of the site. During the registration process we require you to provide us with information that personally identifies you, such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and an account password. This information is collectively referred to as “personal information”. We also ask that you provide us with credit card or other payment account information (“payment information”) which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. 

We receive and store any personal information and/or payment information you enter anywhere on the site, as well as any communications you send to us. 

Additionally, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type and language, cookie information and the page you request. This information is helpful for marketing purposes and for improving your experience on the site. 

To protect against fraud and other misconduct, we may collect information about your interaction with our services, and your posts will contain account identifying information which only Binverse can decode. 

We may retain e-mail or other communications you send to Binverse in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

Binverse’s services are supplied by third parties. Personal information may be sent to those third parties to deliver the services. Third parties providing services to Binverse may have different privacy policies. 

Your account usage is only monitored for the purpose of tracking your download allotment and does not include tracking of specific downloads or posts, although your posts can be traced to you for abuse purposes through account identifying information inserted in your post which only Binverse can decode. 

Binverse’s downloadable Usenet browsing software does not collect any personal information or payment information. 

##  HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE GATHER 

Binverse uses the personal information you provide for the following purposes:   

  * providing you with our services, including the display of customized content;
  * responding to your requests and inquiries, informing you of special offers and otherwise communicating with you;
  * research and analysis (including trend analysis and pattern detection) to maintain, protect and improve our services;
  * site and system administration to ensure that the site and the services function as intended; and
  * developing new services.

We may also share your personal information as described below. Except as provided herein, we will not release your personal information to a third party unless you have granted us permission to do so.

Binverse processes personal information and/or payment information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. 

##  HOW WE USE "COOKIES" 

A “cookie” is a small file stored on your hard drive containing information about you. Binverse, like many other companies, uses cookies to collect information 

Binverse uses cookies to uniquely identify your browser, store your preferences and “remember” you. Cookies can also help Binverse see which areas of the site are popular and which are not, allowing Binverse to improve and update the site based on data such as total number of visitors and pages viewed. 

We do not store any personal information or payment information in cookies. 

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but allow you to instruct your browser to prevent the use of cookies. (The “Help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether). If you disable cookies, you may still use our site, but certain aspects of the experience may be impacted. 

##  SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

We work closely with third parties to bring you our services. In that regard, we may share personal information, payment information and/or other information you provide when another company is involved so that company can perform its functions. Examples include sending postal mail and e-mail, and processing credit card payments. These third parties have access to information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. We may terminate our relationship or take other appropriate action if we determine they are using information improperly. 

Binverse restricts access to personal information and payment information to its employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information to operate, develop or improve our services. These parties are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet those obligations. 

##  ADDITIONAL COMMUNICATIONS 

We may direct additional communications, including e-mail, to registered customers that we deem may be of interest to them. To be removed from future Binverse e-mail campaigns ("opt out" request) you can access and update your information on our Site. 

##  LINKS TO OTHER SITES 

Our Site may contain links to other web sites. We try to make sure that these links are to other, helpful web sites, but you should be aware that when you click on links and/or ad banners that take you to third-party web sites, you will be subject to the third parties' privacy policies, not ours. While we support the protection of privacy on the Internet, we are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third parties and other web sites. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement and user terms and conditions whenever interacting with, and prior to providing any personal information to, any other web site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Company on this Site. 

##  YOUR SECURITY 

While we make reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or information we transmit to you from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. 

##  LOST OR STOLEN INFORMATION 

You must promptly notify us if your user name or password is lost, stolen, or used without permission. In such an event, we will note that you have canceled your user name or password in our system and will update our records accordingly. 

##  HOW TO LIMIT THE USE OF YOUR INFORMATION 

We give users the opportunity to "opt out" of having their personal information used for purposes not directly related to the operation of the service at the point where we ask for the information. If you prefer to "opt out" and not have us send you material we think may be of interest to you, such as promotional mailings/e-mails from us and sites and companies we own or work with, then you can notify us by logging on to your account at [http://www.binverse.com](http://www.binverse.com/) and selecting Email Preferences or by writing to us at: 2125 Center Avenue Suite 507 Fort Lee, NJ 07024\. Your instructions to limit the use of your information will be processed as soon as reasonably practicable. 

##  UPDATING OR CORRECTING INFORMATION 

We rely on our users to update or correct their personal information or payment information whenever necessary. You may access and update your information on our Site. Alternatively, if any of your personal information and/or payment information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, we will correct, update, or remove (unless we are required by law to retain such information) that personal data provided to us. This can be done by using Binverse’s support contact form. The e-mail must identify yourself and the information you are requesting be corrected, updated or removed. We may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (such as requests concerning information on back-up tapes). 

##  YOUR CONSENT AND CHANGES TO THIS POLICY 

By using our Site, you consent to the collection and use of information by us in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our Site so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. By continuing to use this site after notice is given, you will have consented to our use of your information in this different manner. If at any time you would like notice of changes to the Privacy Policy, contact us using Binverse’s support contact form

##  DISCLOSURE REQUIRED BY LAW 

We may disclose personal information and/or payment information when required by law or when we believe in good faith that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a court order or legal process served upon Binverse or any of its officers or principals. When asked, Binverse will provide support to law enforcement by acknowledging the existence of information and providing language that particularly describes the information being sought. Binverse will not divulge the fact of a criminal investigation. 

We further reserve the right to disclose such information when Binverse reasonably believes that it is needed to identify, contact, or bring legal action against a party who may be violating Binverse's Terms of Use or may be causing injury to or interference with Binverse's rights or property, registered customers or potential customers of Binverse, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. 

##  ENFORCEMENT 

Binverse regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or Binverse’s treatment of personal information and/or payment information by contacting us using Binverse’s support contact form or by writing to us at: 

2125 Center Avenue Suite 507  
Fort Lee, NJ 07024  
USA

When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is Binverse’s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. 

In case of disputes, individuals can seek resolution of their questions or complaints regarding use and disclosure of their personal data in accordance with the principles contained in this policy. If you feel that Binverse is not abiding by this policy, you should first contact Binverse using the contact information provided above.
